Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Fanzine Collection, 1948-2019 RL.00925
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Fanzines, 1952-2003, 24 boxes
  - Storyboard: The Art of Laughter, Vol. I, 1; Vol.II, 1-5; Vol. III, 1-2, 4 (1991-1992) (Box 361)
  - Stripper, 10 (1975) (Box 372)
  - Super Adventures, 8-9 (1968) (Box 355)
  - Syndrome, 1 (1971) (Box 371)
  - T.H.U.M.B. Bulletin, 4-5,7 (1971-1972) (Box 353)
  - Tabebuian, 13,16 (1974) (Box 371)
  - Tandstikkerzeitung, 1-10 (1973-1977) (Box 354)
  - Tanstaafl, 8 (1969) (Box 363)
  - TCF, 3 (1975) (Box 355)
  - Ten-Oh-Five Willow, 1 (1977) (Box 371)
  - Tidewater Mini-Con Newsletter, 4 (1975) (Box 355)
  - Tight Beam, 71 (1972) (Box 353)
  - Tight Beam, 60-64 (1970) (Box 369)
  - Timely Comic Index, 1 (1969) (Box 352)
  - Tint, 1 (1966) (Box 358)
  - Tolkien Journal, Vol. I, 1; Vol. II, 1-4; Vol. III, 1-4; Vol. IV, 1-2,5 (1965-1970) (Box 369)
  - Treatise on Reality in Comic Literature, A, 1 (1976) (Box 351)
  - Trefoil, 1-100 (1977-1982) (Box 367)
    Published by Edwin Murray
  - Trivializing Pigeons in the Park, (undated) (Box 371)
  - Turok: Son of Stone Checklist, 1 (1978) (Box 358)
  - Umbra, 6 (1973) (Box 355)
  - Umbra, Vol. I, 4 (undated) (Box 371)
  - Universe, 1 (1975) (Box 371)
  - Unter Helios, 2-3 (1974) (Box 371)
    Contains history of underground comics
  - Vacation in Duckburg, 1-2 (1971) (Box 361)
  - Various Donald Duck Strip Reprints, (undated) (Box 362)
  - Various Flyers, (undated) (Box 362)
    Contains flyer for the First Symposium on Donald Duck held 1970 April 10 at Duke University
  - Vert, 3 (1977) (Box 371)
  - Vertigo, 1-43 (1969-1980) (Box 367)
  - Voice of Comicdom, 4-5 (1965) (Box 356)
  - Vosfan, 20 (1972) (Box 370)
  - Warehouse, 1-5 (1972-1976) (Box 363)
  - Washington Metropolitan Area Comic Art Newsletter, 1-2 (1974) (Box 355)
    Published by Gary Groth
  - Weirdom, Vol. II, 2-3 (1966) (Box 371)
  - The Whole Fanzine Catalog, 3 (1978) (Box 372)
  - The Who's Who in American Comic Books, Vol. I-IV (1973-1976) (Box 351)
  - Witzend, 1-12 (1967-1982) (Box 358)
  - The World and Others, 1 (undated) (Box 363)
  - XYTOCIC, 11 (1974) (Box 355)
  - Yancy Street Journal, 7-12 (1965) (Box 356)
  - Yandro, 167,199,210,213-215,217,219,221,223,226-227,229 (1967-1974) (Box 369)
  - Ye Gods, 1 (1972) (Box 363)
  - Yellow Balloon, 6 (1972) (Box 371)
  - Ymir, Vol. II, 1 (Box 370)
- Accession (2010-0107), 7 boxes
  This addition may include overlapping titles.
  - Rocket Blast Comicollector Issues 8, 33, 35, 37-49, 51-84 (Box Z1)
  - Rocket Blast Comicollector Issues 85-130 (Box Z2)
  - Rocket Blast Comicollector Issues 131-153 (Box Z3)
  - It Goes on the Shelf, 20 (May 1999) (Box Z4)
  - Fantasy Mongers, 1983 (Box Z4)
  - Hickman, Lynn. TLMA, 1 (June 1951) (Box Z4)
  - Fantasy Times, Vol. 6, 22 (Nov. 1951) (Box Z4)
  - Love, Vol. 1, 1-3 and 6 (Oct. 1965-Aug. 1966) (Box Z4)
  - ERB Zine, 2009 (Box Z4)
  - Chamber of Horrors, 2, 3, 5, 7, and 8 (Box Z4)
  - Spectre, 20 and 21 (1989) (Box Z4)
  - Fighting Hero Comics, 4 (undated) (Box Z4)
  - Star Studded Comics, 2, 4-17 (Sept. 1963-Summer 1971) (Box Z4)
  - Blank in the Comics, 29-32, 45-47 (1986) (Box Z5)
  - Flying Founder Review, 1, Vol. 2 no. 6-Vol. 2 no. 8 (1986) (Box Z5)
  - DAPA-EM - Elementary, 15 (1977) (Box Z5)
  - The Greater Days of Westerns, 2-4 (date unknown) (Box Z5)
  - The Naked Id, 14 (1986) (Box Z5)
  - Robert E. Howard United Press Association, 16-17 (1975) (Box Z5)
  - Science Fiction Review (formerly Psychotic), 29-43 (1969-1971), 4 folders (Box Z6)
  - Richard E. Geis, 1-3 (1972) (Box Z6)
  - The Alien Critic (formerly Richard E. Geis), 5-11 (1973-1974), 2 folders (Box Z6)
  - Science Fiction Review (formerly The Alien Critic), 12-61 (1975-1986), 12 folders (Box Z6)
  - Controversy in Review, 15 and 17 (1987) (Box Z6)
  - Norb's Notes, 1-100 (1960-1966) (Box Z7)
  - Cartaggio, 11 (1981) (Box Z7)
  - The Menomonee Falls Guardian Alley Oop Special, 1 (1973) (Box Z7)
  - Nostalgia News, 20-22, (1973) (Box Z7)
  - Yesterday's Comics, 1-3 (1974) (Box Z7)
  - Street Comix, 1-2 (1973) (Box Z7)
  - The Cisco Kid, 1 (1973) (Box Z7)
  - Krazy Kat, 1 (1973) (Box Z7)
  - Jungle Gym, 1 (1972) (Box Z7)
  - Prince Valient, 1 (1972) (Box Z7)
- Accession (2019-0078), 1948-2019
  - The Mystery Fancier, 1977-1988 (Box Z8)
  - The Adventures Continue, 1989-1997 (Box Z8)
  - Science Fiction Studies, 2016 (Box Z8)
  - Extrapolations, 2015-2016 (Box Z8)
  - The New York Review of Science Fiction, 1998-2013 (Box Z9)
  - Science Fiction Chronicle, 1980 (Box Z9)
  - Star Trek Communicator, 1999-2014 (Box Z10)
  - Science Fiction Research Association Review, 1999-2013 (Box Z11)
  - Previews, 2012-2013 (Box Z11)
  - Previews, 2011, 2017-2018 (Box Z12)
  - Previews, 2017 (Box Z13)
  - Game Trade Magazine, 2011, 2017-2019 (Box Z13)
  - image+, 2017-2018 (Box Z13)
  - Star Wars Insider, 2007-2014 (Box Z14)
  - image+, 2018 (Box Z14)
  - Game Trade Magazine, 2011, 2018 (Box Z14)
  - The Return of Superman, 2013 (Box Z14)
  - The Death of Superman, 2013 (Box Z14)
  - World Without a Superman, 2013 (Box Z14)
  - James Bond, 1990 (Box Z14)
  - Dick Tracy Magazine, 1992-2003 (Box Z15)
  - Locus, 2000-2007 (Box Z16)
  - Locus, 1999-2000, 2007-2012 (Box Z17)
  - Knights of the Dinner Table, 1998-2004 (Box Z18)
  - Knights of the Dinner Table, 2004-2012 (Box Z19)
  - Knights of the Dinner Table, 2012-2014 (Box Z20)
  - Foundation, 1979, 2000-2011 (Box Z20)
  - The baum bugle, 1974 (Box Z20)
  - Strip Scene, 1977-1982 (Box Z20)
  - Adventure Scene, undated (Box Z20)
  - Comic Detective Research Society, 1971-1973 (Box Z20)
  - Edgar Rice Burroughs fanzines, 1959-1974 (Box Z21)
  - Lovecraft Studies, 1985-1987 (Box Z21)
  - Studies in Weird Fiction, 1988 (Box Z21)
  - Roebrt E. Howard fanzines, 1974-1975, 1989-1990 (Box Z21)
  - Shadow, 1973 (Box Z21)
  - Outre, 1994 (Box Z21)
  - FXRH, 1972-1973 (Box Z21)
  - Ray Harrison fanzines, 1971, 1993 (Box Z21)
  - Closeup, 1975-1977 (Box Z21)
  - Erbatnia, 1960-1975 (Box Z21)
  - Roundup, 2012-2013 (Box Z21)
  - Newsboy, 2011-2014 (Box Z21)
  - Tim Marion fanzines, 2002-2008 (Box Z21)
  - 20 unanswered questions to 9/11, 2003 (Box Z21)
  - The Howard Collector, 1961-1973 (Box Z21)
  - ERBzine (Edgar Rice Burroughs webzine), 2009-2011 (Box Z22)
  - Writings by James D. Keeline, 1998-2014 (Box Z23)
  - Rick Brant web fanzine printout (www.rickbrant.com), 2007-2011 (Box Z23)
  - The Unofficial Tom Swift Home Page web printout, 2007 (Box Z23)
  - Web printouts, 2007 (Box Z23)
  - Sword and Fantasy, 2005-2008 (Box Z23)
  - Fantastic Worlds, 1953 (Box Z23)
  - Fanciful Tales of Time and Space, 1977 (Box Z23)
  - Psychotic, 1955 (Box Z23)
  - Destiny, 1954 (Box Z23)
  - Inside and Science Fiction Advertiser, 1955 (Box Z23)
  - Fantasy Advertiser, 1948 (Box Z23)
  - Omnifan, 1974 (Box Z23)
  - The Diversifier, 1976-1978 (Box Z23)
  - The Howard Review, 1975 (Box Z23)
  - Phantasy Digest, 1976-1977 (Box Z23)
  - Teaching SF, 1972 (Box Z23)
  - fantasy macabre, 1981 (Box Z23)
  - Yellowback library, 2003-2018 (Box Z24)
  - Fantasy crossroads, 1974-1979 (Box Z24)
  - REH: Two-Gun Raconteur, 1976-1977 (Box Z24)
  - Chacal, 1976-1977 (Box Z24)
  - REH: Lone Star Fictioneer, 1975-1976 (Box Z24)
  - escape!, 1977 (Box Z24)
  - Runes of ahrh-eih-ache, 1976 (Box Z24)
  - Erased from Exile, 1976 (Box Z24)
  - Fantasy Crosswinds, 1977 (Box Z24)
  - Fantome, 1978 (Box Z24)
  - Crifanac, 1998 (Box Z24)
  - The Distant Suns, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - Night Views, 1977 (Box Z24)
  - Oopsla!, 1952 (Box Z24)
  - Dark Phantasms, 1976 (Box Z24)
  - Space-Ship, 1953 (Box Z24)
  - The Fillostrated Fan Dictionary, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - Tangent, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - DOC, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - The Andover Road Journal, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - Starwind, 1976 (Box Z24)
  - Mesmeridian, 1973 (Box Z24)
  - Cartoon, 1971-1973 (Box Z24)
  - THR, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - Knights, 1973 (Box Z24)
  - The avenger, 1974 (Box Z24)
  - Whizzard, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - The Howard Review, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - ACBA Sketchbook, 1975 (Box Z24)
  - The Adventures of Lord Blackstone, 1985 (Box Z25)
  - Normal Bean News, 1985 (Box Z25)
  - Heroic Fantasy Series, undated (Box Z25)
  - The Cry of the Pheonix, undated (Box Z25)
  - Popilania, 1980 (Box Z25)
  - Capnap News, 1983 (Box Z25)
  - Callthump, 1984 (Box Z25)
  - Captain George's Whizbang, 1969-1974 (Box Z25)
  - The Movies, undated (Box Z25)
  - The Wonderful World of Comics, undated (Box Z25)
  - Captain George's Comic World, 1940s-1950s (Box Z25)
  - Toons for our Times, 1984 (Box Z25)
  - Casey Ruggles, 1952-1954 (Box Z25)
- Accession (2019-0103), 1960-2009
  - Fantasy Review, 1979-1987 (Box Z26)
  - The Miscast Barbarian, 1975 (Box Z27)
  - Avalon to Camelot, 1983-1987 (Box Z27)
  - Xenophile, 1974-1980 (Box Z27)
  - American Fantasy, 1982 (Box Z28)
  - The Films of Yesteryear, 1981 (Box Z28)
  - The World of Yesterday, 1978-1979 (Box Z28)
  - Under Western Skies, 1978 (Box Z28)
  - Color Collectors Guide, 1990 (Box Z28)
  - CinemaScore, 1983 (Box Z28)
  - Questar, 1980 (Box Z28)
  - Ethics & Odyssey, 1973-1987 (Box Z28)
  - The Third Alternative, 2000 (Box Z28)
  - Suspense, 1997 (Box Z28)
  - The Patchin Review, 1983 (Box Z28)
  - New Libertarian Notes, 1974 (Box Z28)
  - Weirdbook, 1968-1988 (Box Z28)
  - World Fantasy Convention, 1983-1990 (Box Z28)
  - JDMBibliophile, 1967-1992 (Box Z28)
  - Collecting Paperbacks?, 1979-1983 (Box Z29)
  - Doc Shadow Quarterly, 1981-1985 (Box Z29)
  - The ParkerPhile, 1983 (Box Z29)
  - The Rohmer Review, 1968-1981 (Box Z29)
  - Amra: Swordplay & Sorcery, 1960-1982 (Box Z29)
  - Not of this Earth, 1993, 1994 (Box Z30)
  - Argosy, 1974 (Box Z30)
  - Starlog, 1995 (Box Z30)
  - Writer's Digest, 1980 (Box Z30)
  - Mystery, 1980-1982 (Box Z30)
  - The Mystery Review, 1998-2000 (Box Z30)
  - New Mystery, 1999 (Box Z30)
  - Sci-Fi Universe, 1997 (Box Z30)
  - Hardboiled, 1985 (Box Z30)
  - Who Was that Monolith I Saw You With?, 1976 (Box Z30)
  - Cartoonews, 1975-1979 (Box Z30)
  - Disney twenty-three, 2009 (Box Z30)
  - Storyboard: the Art of Laughter, 1992-1994 (Box Z30)
  - Sci-Fi Invasion, 1998 (Box Z30)
  - Retro-Vision (Box Z30)
  - Sentai, 1994 (Box Z30)
  - Oriental Cinema, 1994 (Box Z30)
  - Babylon 5, 1995 (Box Z30)
  - Legendary Heroes, 1997 (Box Z30)
  - Cinescape, 1995, 1998 (Box Z30)
  - Spectrum, 1994, 1997 (Box Z30)
  - Mystery Scene, 1987-1999 (Box Z30)